I don't believe that you could become an
AI first organization talking about AI
and delivering AI
>> [music]
>> unless you've been through that journey
and understand what that looks like.
For me, becoming frontier firm is a is a
state of mind and it's the way that
[music] we think about challenges and
reinvent processes. We knew we had a
challenge with lots of disparate systems
cuz and we knew to [music] embrace AI we
needed to consolidate all of that data
into one place so that we could unlock
all of the the value that was there.
The customer zero journey has [music]
touched every element of our
organization and it enables the
departments now to become change agents.
It's giving tons of capacity back into
my team. Um we've automated a number of
workflows including [music] supplier
invoicing. It's enabled the team to
focus on more important anonymization
and strategic [music] initiatives.
That's allowed us to grow by 40% over
the last year with the same head count
that we had 2 years ago
uh and operational savings of 1 and 1/2.
So for Infinity Group the business
impact has been truly transformational.
We've gone from local [music] IT
provider to global business central
partner of the year in the space of 3
years. Because it allows us to talk with
authenticity to our [music] clients
about the technology we're using and how
we're using it within our organization.
It's had a huge impact on our culture.
It's really delivering value for us
allowing our people to do more important
[music] work. I think probably the
biggest success that we've had is the
opportunity for new people to come into
[music] the business and not feel left
behind because ideally we've spent quite
a bit of time um prepping ourselves,
practicing with AI.
>> [music]
>> And so everybody's learning, everybody's
talking about it and there's a general
passion and interest.
Partners, if I was to give you three
bits of advice, it would be this. Number
one,
understand your business challenges,
talk to your teams,
>> [music]
>> find the bottlenecks.
Number two, get your data sorted out.
Cannot underestimate [music] how
important that is. And number three,
take your people on the journey.
They may feel threatened,
but you want to make them feel
empowered. You know, we're moving into a
world where [music] AI is just
transforming the way that we work and
the way that we deliver services.
If you really want to transform your
clients, you need to [music] start by
transforming yourself first.